Finding Aid for Shirley Wheeler Smith Papers, 1881-1959
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Miscellaneous; include portraits of Smith and his wife, Sara Browne Smith; group portrait of 1897 Michiganensian board; group portrait of University of Michigan students from Barry County, Michigan, 1894 photograph of employees of Hastings Wool Boot Company (Box 15)
Apr. 2, 1952, Apr. 29, 1955, Nov. 8, 1957, Nov. 12, 1957
Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.
Aug. 12, 1934
Haynes, Harley Armand, 1875-
Feb. 25, 1952, Mar. 17, 1952, Mar. 23, 1952, Mar. 30, 1952
Henderson, William D., 1866.
Sept. 14, 1921
Herbert, J. Joseph, 1894-1956.
Jan. 31, 1956, Feb. 13, 1956
Hinsdale, W. B. (Wilbert B.), 1851-1944.
May 20, 1924, Dec. 25, 1925
Hoad, William Christian, 1874-1962.
Apr. 21, 1926, Dec. 14, 1931, Apr. 24, 1933, May 23, 1933, Mar. 28, 1935, Nov. 18, 1936, Jan. 1940, Oct. 27, 1941, May 3, 1945, Dec. 1, 1948, Mar. 15, 1951, Mar. 29, 1951, Dec. 21, 1951, Feb. 7, 1953, Oct. 27, 1953, Oct. 21, 1954
Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1952.
Jan. 4, 1937
Hodges, Fred Jenner, 1895-
Jan. 27, 1938, Jan. 28, 1938
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.
Jan. 1932, Mar. 28, 1935, May 17, 1935, June 6, 1935, July 25, 1935
Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.
Aug. 31, 1921, Sept. 3, 1927, Jan. 17, 1930, Jan. 23, 1933
Hussey, William Joseph, 1862-1926.
Jan. 10, 1917
Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.
Nov. 14, 1910, Apr. 9, 1919, Apr. 12, 1921, May 16, 1927, Aug. 13, 1927
Hutchins, Harry Crocker, 1880-1948.
Oct. 2, 1945, Oct. 8, 1945, Oct. 11, 1945, Oct. 17, 1945, Oct. 19, 1945, Oct. 31, 1945, Nov. 3, 1945, Nov. 6, 1945, Feb. 15, 1946, Feb. 20, 1946
Iden, Thomas Medary, 1856-1933.
Apr. 10, 1931
Jones, Samuel Arthur, 1834-1912.
Jan. 26, 1897
Keatley, Vivien B. (Vivien Bulloch), 1909-
Dec. 2, 1946, Nov. 5, 1947, Dec. 22, 1947, Apr. 15, 1948, Apr. 26, 1948, May 1, 1948, Oct. 28, 1948, June 23, 1951, Aug. 17, 1951
Kelly, .Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.
July 12, 1940, July 19, 1940, July 12, 1944, Nov. 1, 1946
Kemp, Edward Gearing, 1887-1962.
Feb. 5, 1937
Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.
Oct. 4, 1902, Sept. 19, 1904, Nov. 28, 1907, Mar. 30, 1911
Knutson, Harold, 1880-1963.
Jan. 6, 1948
Lane, Victor Hugo, 1852-1930.
July 8, 1901, July 25, 1902, June 10, 1908, Aug. 27, 1921
Lawrence, David Leo, 1889-1966.
Jan. 29, 1951, Mar. 4, 1951, Mar. 8, 1951, Mar. 17, 1951
Leland, Frank Bruce.
Mar. 31, 1923, Apr. 4, 1923
Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), 1888.
July 8, 1925, July 11, 1926, May 31, 1927, Sept. 27, 1927, Apr. 11, 1931
Lloyd, Alice Crocker, 1893-1950.
Mar. 17, 1943, Mar. 19, 1943, Mar. 17, 1946
Lombard, Warren P. (Warren Plimpton), 1855-1939.
May 9, 1923
Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.
Mar. 14, 1930
McCallum, George P. (George Porterfield), 1871-1952.
Dec. 5, 1938
McClure, Harry H.
June 7, 1893, July 20, 1899, Aug. 2, 1899, July 28, 1900, Aug. 12, 1901, May 19, 1902
MacLachlan, James Angell, 1891-
May 13, 1955, May, 17, 1955, May 23, 1955, June 12, 1955, June 20, 1955
McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947.
May 13, 1899, Jan. 13, 1904, May 12, 1936, May 16, 1936, Oct. 21, 1941, Mar. 27, 1944
McPeek, Russell Roy, 1862-1945.
Mar. 9, 1923, Oct. 2, 1930, Oct. 6, 1930, Nov. 4, 1930, Feb. 24, 1931, Mar. 3, 1931, Feb. 16, 1932, May 9, 1932, Nov. 3, 1932, Nov. 4, 1932, Nov. 23, 1932, 1933-1945
Maddy, Joseph E. (Joseph Edgar), 1891-1966.
June 20, 1941, June 23, 1941
Markley, Mary Elizabeth B., 1864-1956.
Apr. 24, 1930, Aug. 9, 1949
Mattern, David Earl, 1890-1959.
June 5, 1945, Mar. 27, 1947
Meader, George, 1907-
Jan. 17, 1951, Mar. 4, 1952, Mar. 6, 1952, Mar. 22, 1952
Mechem, Floyd R. (Floyd Russell), 1858-1928.
Mar. 18, 1901
Michener, Earl C. (Early Cory), 1876-1957.
Nov. 22, 1932, July 16, 1934, Nov. 19, 1934, Mar. 23, 1942, Mar. 25, 1942, Apr. 21, 1942, May 8, 1942, May 15, 1942, Sept. 28, 1942, Apr. 17, 1943, Apr. 19, 1943, Apr. 22, 1943, Nov. 21, 1946, Feb. 11, 1947, Feb. 13, 1947
Jan. 3, 1948, Jan. 6, 1948, Sept. 16, 1948, May 19, 1949, May 23, 1949, Mar. 16, 1950, Mar. 18, 1950, June 7, 1950, Aug. 16, 1950, Aug. 19, 1950, Aug. 23, 1950, Aug. 25, 1950, Jan. 10, 1951
Moffit, John Ted, 1862-1947.
July 27, 1945
Moore, Earl Vincent, 1890-1987.
Jan. 16, 1951
Morrill, James Lewis, 1891-
Aug 9, 1955, Aug. 14, 1955
Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.
Apr. 17, 1922, July 5, 1927, Nov. 23, 1933, July 12, 1934, Jan. 7, 1935, Jan. 10, 1935, Jan. 4, 1938, June 13, 1938, Dec. 14, 1938, Sept. 18, 1939, Apr. 16, 1940, June 10, 1940
Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.
Mar. 15, 1937, Dec. 5, 1939
Nelson, J. Raleigh (Joseph Raleigh)
Sept. 14, 1951
Newcombe, Frederick Charles, 1858-1927.
Apr. 9, 1912
Newkirk, Henry Wirt, 1854-1946.
Aug. 8, 1932
Novy, Frederick George, 1864-1957.
Jan. 26, 1953, Dec. 8, 1955
Okkelberg, Peter Olaus, 1880-
Mar. 12, 1950
Orr, H. Winnett (Hiram Winnett), 1877-1956.
July 14, 1948
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), 1860
Dec. 27, 1910, Nov. 15, 1930, Nov. 21, 1930, Dec. 26, 1930, Jan. 22, 1931, May 18, 1931, Jan. 8, 1932, Sept. 8, 1934, Sept. 17, 1934, Mar. 3, 1936, May 5, 1937, May 21, 1937, Nov. 18, 1939, Apr. 2, 1940, May 24, 1940, Dec. 24, 1941, Nov. 20, 1945
Otis, Robert Burns, 1879-
Nov. 5, 1956, Nov. 24, 1956
Parker, Edward Foster.
Feb. 9, 1932, Dec. 21, 1954
Patterson, Robert Porter, 1891-1952.
May 4, 1944 [To A. H. Vandenberg], May 29, 1944 [To A. H. Vandenberg]
Patton, Carl S. (Carl Safford), 1891-1952.
Mar. 1, 1904, Sept. 21, 1927, Nov. 15, 1927, Oct. 14, 1935, Oct. 21, 1935
Perkins, John A. (John Alanson), 1914-
Nov. 14, 1950, Mar. 14, 1956
Peterson, Reuben, 1862-1942.
Jan. 5, 1931, Oct. 21, 1938, Oct. 26, 1938
Phelps, William Lyon, 1868-1943.
July 23, 1935, July 25, 1935
Pillsbury, W. B. (Walter Bowers), 1872-1960.
May 13, 1942
Pollock, James Kerr, 1898-
May 17, 1945, May 22, 1945, May 24, 1945
Potter, Louise, 1895-
Feb. 25, 1930, July 9, 1930, July 22, 1930, Nov. 7, 1935, Nov. 9, 1935, Nov. 15, 1935
Power, Eugene B., 1905-
Jan. 2, 1956
Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-
Jan. 14, 1931, Apr. 17, 1936, Jan. 19, 1937, Jan. 22, 1937
Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965.
Dec. 27, 1938, Jan. 5, 1930, Aug. 25, 1939, Jan. 2, 1940, Aug. 17, 1940, Feb. 4, 1941, Aug. 11, 1941, Dec. 26, 1942, Dec. 20, 1943, Dec. 31, 1943, Jan. 24, 1944, July 19, 1944, Dec. 20, 1944, Dec. 27, 1944, Dec. 30, 1944
Jan. 24, 1945, Feb. 15, 1945, May 5, 1945, July 17, 1945, July 23, 1945, Aug. 14, 1945, Dec. 31, 1945, July 9, 1946, July 24, 1947, Jan. 7, 1948, Jan. 10, 1948, Dec. 20, 1948, Mar. 10, 1949, Aug. 12, 1949
Feb. 24, 1950, Mar. 20, 1950, July 27, 1950, Jan. 26, 1953, Mar. 5, 1954, Dec. 10, 1954, Dec. 21, 1955, Dec. 17, 1956, Dec. 26, 1957
Reisler, Joseph T.
June 13, 1940, concerning the nomination of Wendell Wilkie, "the only Republican candidate who can be elected."
Rice, Warner Grenelle, 1899-
May 1, 1942, May 26, 1949, Mar. 12, 1951, Nov. 7, 1951, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug. 21, 1952
Riggs, Henry Earle, 1865.
Apr. 26, 1923, Mar. 5, 1940, Mar. 20, 1944, Mar. 26, 1944, Mar. 28 1944, June 8, 1944, May 4, 1945, May 9, 1945, Sept. 6, 1945, 1946 undated, May 26, 1949, May 29, 1949
Robertson, James H. (James Holman), 1915-
Jan. 12, 1951
Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943.
May 2, 1940
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.
Jan. 1932
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
July 16, 1931, Aug. 3, 1931, Aug.19, 1931, Mar. 12, 1932, Aug. 4, 1933, July 4, 1934, Sept. 1, 1934, Oct. 12, 1934, Oct. 22, 1934, Nov. 14, 1934, Jul. 19, 1935, July 20, 1935, July 22, 1935, Dec. 3, 1935, 1935 undated, July 20, 1936, Aug. 22, 1936, July 28, 1937, Aug. 11, 1939
June 17, 1942, Oct. 9, 1942, Nov. 24, 1943, June 5, 1944, July 19, 1944, July 26, 1944, Aug. 5, 1944, Nov. 1, 1944, Nov. 13, 1944, Dec. 25, 1944, Feb. 24, 1945, Apr. 12, 1945, 1946 undated, Mar. 19, 1948, Mar. 20, 1951, Apr. 1951, May 25, 1951, Dec. 5, 1951, Dec. 26, 1952, Jan. 5, 1954, Dec. 28, 1954, Jan. 2, 1957, Dec. 30, 1957
Sample, George Washington, 1868-1945.
May 5, 1934, Jan. 7, 1935, Jan. 8, 1935
Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.
Mar. 11, 1910, Mar. 14, 1910, Apr. 10, 1910, Apr. 13, 1910, Jan. 12, 1912, Apr. 10, 1913, Feb. 28, 1920, Jan 14, 1930, May 10, 1930, Dec. 22, 1930, Mar. 1, 1920, Mar. 9, 1920, Mar. 3, 1924, May 13, 1924, Aug. 21, 1924
Aug. 5, 1925, Mar. 7, 1926, May 13, 1926, Jan. 11, 1927, Apr. 30, 1927, May 19, 1927, June 28, 1927, Sept. 3, 1927, Feb. 28, 1928, Oct. 7, 1928, Dec. 17, 1928, Jan. 14, 1930
Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931.
May 13, 1899, July 7, 1899, July 13, 1899, Mar. 23, 1922, Jan. 22, 1927, Mar. 9, 1927, July 25, 1927
Scott, Georgia Jackson.
1930-1932
Shaw, Wilfred Byron, 1881-1959.
Jan. 31, 1905, Feb. 11, 1905, Apr. 23, 1948, Oct. 18, 1948
Shields, Edmund Claude, 1871-1947.
Apr. 5, 1935, Jan. 10, 1936, Feb. 16, 1937, Feb. 24, 1937, Apr. 27, 1937, Jan. 2, 1946
Shorts, Robert Perry, 1879-
Mar. 23, 1934
Sigler, Kim, 1894.
Sept. 18, 1934, Apr. 24, 1937, Sept. 14, 1937, Sept. 16, 1937, Sept. 18, 1937, Sept. 21, 1937, Sept. 23, 1937, Nov. 3, 1937, Dec. 9, 1946, Mar. 13, 1947, Feb. 2, 1948
Sink, Charles Albert, 1879-1972.
Mar. 2, 1912, Apr. 15, 1913, Jan. 20, 1932, Sept. 28, 1932, Oct. 13, 1932, Oct. 21, 1932, Jan. 2, 1936, Sept. 30, 1937, Jan. 28, 1938, Jan. 22, 1940, Jan. 23, 1940, Feb. 9, 1940, Feb. 15, 1940, Mar. 17, 1942, Apr. 28, 1942, July 11, 1943, Dec. 16, 1943
Dec. 13, 1946, Mar. 4, 1947, Mar. 7, 1947, Jan. 18, 1949, Mar. 4, 1949, Apr. 18, 1949, Mar. 30, 1950, Apr. 3, 1950, Dec. 7, 1950, Apr. 17, 1951, Nov. 8, 1951, Dec. 3, 1951, Jan. 9, 1952, Mar. 26, 1952, Apr. 21, 1953, Sept. 17, 1953, Apr. 14, 1954
Apr. 27, 1955, Nov. 4, 1956, Mar. 21, 1956, July 18, 1956, Nov. 12, 1956, Mar. 27, 1957, Apr. 1, 1957, Apr. 20, 1957, May 20, 1957, May 21, 1957, June 11, 1957
Slosson, Preston William, 1892-
Jan. 12, 1934, Jan. 16, 1934, June 30, 1945, July 25, 1945, Nov. 17, 1952, Nov. 22, 1952, Aug. 2, 1953
Smith, Clement McDonald, 1844-1923.
1899-1923
Smith, Elbert V.,1864-
Jan. 23, 1918, Mar. 3, 1930, Mar. 20, 1930, Dec. 23, 1930, Aug. 31, 1933, Sept. 1, 1933, Sept. 8, 1933, Sept. 12, 1933, Sept. 15, 1933, Sept. 26, 1933, Sept. 29, 1933, Apr. 21, 1934, Mar. 14, 1935, Feb. 27, 1936, Mar. 16, 1937, Dec. 25, 1938, 1940-1941
Smith, Richard Root, 1869-1940.
Aug. 14, 1933
Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.
Apr. 11, 1917, Apr. 13, 1917
Spill, William Ambrose, 1876-.
Dec. 25, 1924, Feb. 16, 1925, Dec. 19, 1933, Aug. 24, 1936, June 22, 1937, June 27, 1937
Sproul, .Robert Gordon, 1891-1975.
Feb. 16, 1932, Aug. 28, 1952, Oct. 6, 1952
Staebler, Edward William, 1872-1946.
Apr. 16, 1931, Apr. 20, 1931
Staebler, Neil, 1905-
Mar. 12, 1928, Nov. 22, 1946
Stanley, Albert A. (Albert Augustus), 1851-1932.
May 24, 1921, Apr. 28, 1922
Starr, Floyd Elliot, 1883-1980.
Sept. 22, 1948
Stason, E. Blythe (Edwin Blythe), 1891-1972.
May 21, 1951, May 25, 1951
Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.
July 1, 1927, Sept. 9, 1927, Sept. 12, 1927, 1932, Jan. 14, 1933, Jan. 16, 1933, Feb. 23, 1933, Apr. 10, 1933, Feb. 23, 1933, Apr. 10, 1933, Feb. 3, 1934, July 11, 1934, July 16, 1934, July 20, 1934, Aug. 16, 1934, Aug. 23, 1934, Aug. 25, 1934, Nov. 24, 1934
Mar. 22, 1935, Apr. 18, 1935, Feb. 13, 1936, Feb. 15, 1936, Feb. 17, 1936, 1937 undated, Nov. 3, 1937, Dec. 29, 1937, Mar. 6, 1938, Apr. 8, 1938, Apr. 15, 1938
1939 undated, Aug. 10, 1939, Oct. 9, 1939, Oct. 10, 1939, Nov. 10, 1939, Nov. 22, 1939, Nov. 24, 1939, Nov. 27, 1939, Nov. 28, 1939, Jan. 2, 1940, Jan. 8, 1940, Jan. 9, 1940, May 14, 1941, Sept. 8, 1941
Oct. 3, 1945, Oct. 10, 1945, Oct. 18, 1946, Oct. 23, 1946, Nov. 1, 1946, Nov. 2, 1946, Nov. 18, 1946, Sept. 6, 1947, Nov. 8, 1948, May 11, 1949, May 23, 1949, June 1, 1949
Apr. 5, 1950, Apr. 18, 1950, Apr. 21, 1950, June 14, 1950, June 20, 1950, June 23, 1950, June 26, 1950
Apr. 14, 1951, Apr. 22, 1951, Apr. 23, 1951, Aug. 15, 1951, Sept. 19, 1951, Sept. 21, 1951, Sept. 23, 1951, Sept. 26, 1951, Oct. 24, 1951, Oct. 29, 1951, Oct. 31, 1951, Nov. 7, 1951
June 19, 1952, Sept. 17, 1952, Apr. 21, 1953, July 23, 1953, Aug. 4, 1953, Oct. 6, 1953, Oct. 7, 1953, Oct. 8, 1953, Oct.9, 1953, Oct 11, 1953, Oct. 13, 1953, Oct. 14, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953, Nov. 27, 1953, Dec. 9, 1953
Mar. 30, 1954, Apr. 5, 1954, Apr. 21, 1954, July 14, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 16, 1954, Oct. 18, 1954, Oct. 24, 1954, Oct. 28, 1954, Nov. 3, 1954, Nov. 12, 1954, Nov. 13, 1954, Nov. 17, 1954, Nov. 22, 1954, Nov. 26, 1954, Dec. 9, 1954, Dec. 13, 1954, Dec. 17, 1954
1955 undated, Jan. 5, 1955, Jan. 10, 1955, Feb. 24, 1955, Mar. 5, 1955, Mar. 14, 1955, Apr. 5, 1955, Apr. 8, 1955, Feb. 23, 1956, Mar. 12, 1956, Apr. 16, 1956, Apr. 27, 1956, May 7, 1956
Strauss, Louis Abraham, 1872-1938.
June 11, 1934, June 12, 1934
Sullivan, Mark, 1874-1952.
Dec. 30, 1935, Jan. 28, 1936
Summerfield, Arthur Ellsworth, 1899-1972.
Feb. 28, 1953, Apr. 13, 1957
Sundwall, John, 1880-1950.
Feb. 2, 1934, Feb. 8, 1934
Tapping, Theodore Hawley, 1889-1969.
1945, June, 1946, May 6, 1947, Feb. 20, 1948, June 17, 1948, Mar. 1, 1949, May 22, 1950, May 10, 1950, Nov. 21, 1950, May 10, 1952, May 21, 1952, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug. 21, 1952, Apr. 12, 1954, Apr. 16, 1954, May 28, 1954, June 4, 1954, June 21, 1956, Nov. 28, 1956, Nov. 8, 1957, Nov. 21, 1957
Tarbell, Ida M. (Ida Minerva), 1857-1944.
June 13, 1903 [To C. H. Van Tyne concerning Smith]
Taylor, F. M. (Fred Manville), 1855-1932.
Aug. 27, 1925
Thieme, Hugo P. (Hugo Paul), 1870-1940.
Nov. 20, 1923, Nov. 10, 1932, Nov. 19, 1932, Nov. 23, 1932, Feb. 6, 1933, 1934 undated, Nov. 20, 1923
Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.
Apr. 11, 1917, Apr. 13, 1917, May 24, 1917
Trueblood, Thomas Clarkson, 1856-1951.
Apr. 7, 1936, Mar. 31, 1946
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
May 6, 1925, Apr. 30, 1926, Mar. 23, 1923, Apr. 5, 1928, Apr. 7, 1928, Jan. 31, 1934, Feb. 2, 1934, Feb. 5, 1934, Apr. 17, 1934, Apr. 23, 1934, Apr. 25, 1934, Feb. 11, 1936, Feb. 13, 1936, Mar. 5, 1937, Mar. 8, 1937
Apr. 13, 1944, Apr. 15, 1944, Apr. 18, 1944, Apr. 19, 1944, Apr. 20, 1944, May 4, 1944 [Robert P. Patterson to Vandenberg], May 29, 1944 [Robert P. Patterson to Vandenberg], Apr. 21, 1944, Apr. 22, 1944, May 5, 1944, May 8, 1944, May 31, 1944, June 2, 1944, P
June 5, 1945, 1946 undated, Apr. 10, 1946, Apr. 19, 1946, Feb. 11, 1947, Jan. 3, 1948, Jan. 7, 1943, June 13, 1949, June 16, 1949, June 20, 1949, Oct. 9, 1949, Nov. 1, 1949, Jan. 25, 1950, Jan. 28, 1950, Mar. 30, 1950
Vander Velde, Lewis G. (Lewis George), 1890-1975.
Apr. 20, 1938, Oct. 18, 1946, Apr. 10, 1947, Mar. 17, 1950, Apr. 12, 1950, July 14, 1950, June 4, 1951, Dec. 24, 1951, June 9, 1952, July 11, 1952, Feb. 9, 1954, Sept. 20, 1954, Feb. 3, 1955, Mar. 22, 1955, Mar. 30, 1955, Apr. 1, 1957
Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930.
June 3, 1901, June 10, 1903, June 13, 1903 [From Ida Tarbell], Sept. 12, 1905, June 8, 1906, Sept. 14, 1907, Oct. 10, 1907, July 14, 1908, May 20, 1927
Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-
June 29, 1948
Van Zile, Philip T. (Philip Taylor), 1843-1917.
June 27, 1911
Voorhies, Paul Warren, 1875-1952.
Nov. 28, 1930, Dec. 6, 1930
Walter, Erich Albert.
May 10, 1943
Ward, Marcus Llewellyn, 1875-1963.
May 1, 1923, Mar. 12, 1923
Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.
May 1, 1939, May 4, 1939
Wells, Carlton F. (Carlton Frank), 1898-
July 7, 1945
Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.
July 24, 1908
White, Alfred H. (Alfred Holmes), 1873.
Jan. 31, 1917, June 5, 1917, Apr. 23, 1936, Sept. 11, 1936, Oct. 20, 1936, Dec. 13, 1936, Jan. 17, 1942, Apr. 29, 1943, Apr. 28, 1944, Dec. 10, 1942, 1949 undated, Jan. 12, 1952
White, Lee A., 1886.
Oct. 24, 1932
Whitney, Allen Sisson, 1857-1944.
Nov. 30, 1931, Feb. 13, 1933, Feb. 17, 1933
Whitney, Caspar, 1862-1929.
Dec. 28, 1896
Wiley, Merlin, 1875-
Jan. 9, 1923, Oct. 20, 1924, Oct. 24, 1924, Feb. 18, 1925, Sept. 13, 1925, June 2, 1926, May 16, 1940, Apr. 1956
Winter, John Garrett, 1881-1956.
Jan. 12, 1932
Wrentmore, Clarence George, 1867-1934.
June 10, 1908
Wriston, Henry Merritt, 1889-
Dec. 18, 1943, Dec. 22, 1949
Yost, Eunice Josephine Fite, 1881-1975.
Feb. 12, 1954, describing a visit of one of her great aunts with President Lincoln during the Civil War